Two assassins. One secret. No turning back.
Code Name Banshee is a action, thriller film directed by Jon Keeyes.
Caleb, a former government assassin in hiding, who resurfaces when his protégé, the equally
deadly killer known as Banshee, discovers a bounty has been placed on Caleb's head.
Banshee, played by Jaime King.
Caleb, played by Antonio Banderas.
Anthony Greene, played by Tommy Flanagan.
Hailey, played by Catherine Davis.
Carla, played by Kim DeLonghi.
Thug, played by Levon Panek.
Code Name Banshee is a 2022 American action film directed by Jon Keeyes,
starring Jaime King, Antonio Banderas and Tommy Flanagan.
The tone is intense.